A Guide to the Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1977-1981, RG 33 FA1503
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1977-1981; 33
  - Education, 1977-1981; 13
    - Colleges - Princeton University - Contributions (Box 193, Folder 2)
    - Colleges - Princeton University - Fund Raising - Campaign for Princeton (Box 193, Folder 3-4)
    - Colleges - Princeton University - Printed Material (Box 193, Folder 5, Box 194, Folder 1)
    - Colleges - Princeton University - Printed Material - Alumni Weekly (Box 194, Folder 2-3)
    - Colleges - Princeton University - John D. Rockefeller 3rd - A-Z (Box 194, Folder 4)
    - Colleges - Princeton University - John D. Rockefeller 3rd - Board of Trustees (Box 194, Folder 5)
    - Colleges - Princeton University - John D. Rockefeller 3rd - Contributions (Box 194, Folder 6)
    - Colleges - Princeton University - Laurance S. Rockefeller - A-Z (Box 195, Folder 1)
    - Colleges - Princeton University - Laurance S. Rockefeller - Board of Trustees (Box 195, Folder 2)
    - Colleges - Princeton University - Laurance S. Rockefeller - Board of Trustees - A-Z (Box 195, Folder 3-4)
    - Colleges - Princeton University - Laurance S. Rockefeller - Board of Trustees - Art Museum (Box 196, Folder 1)
    - Colleges - Princeton University - Laurance S. Rockefeller - Board of Trustees - Committee on Grounds and Buildings (Box 196, Folder 2)
    - Colleges - Princeton University - Laurance S. Rockefeller - Board of Trustees - Committee on Honorary Degrees (Box 196, Folder 3)
    - Colleges - Princeton University - Laurance S. Rockefeller - Board of Trustees - Committee of Physical Planning and Facilities (Box 196, Folder 4)
    - Colleges - Princeton University - Laurance S. Rockefeller - Board of Trustees - Committee of Physical Planning and Facilities - Forestall Center (Box 196, Folder 5)
    - Colleges - Princeton University - Laurance S. Rockefeller - Board of Trustees - Development Program (Box 196, Folder 6)
    - Colleges - Princeton University - Laurance S. Rockefeller - Board of Trustees - Committee on Real Estate (Box 197, Folder 1)
    - Colleges - Princeton University - Laurance S. Rockefeller - Board of Trustees - Development Program - Harvey S. Firestone Library (Box 197, Folder 2)
    - Colleges - Princeton University - Laurance S. Rockefeller - Board of Trustees - Development Program - A-Z (Box 197, Folder 3)
    - Colleges - Princeton University - Laurance S. Rockefeller - Board of Trustees - Development Program - Alexander Russell Memorial Bench (Box 198, Folder 1)
    - Colleges - Princeton University - Laurance S. Rockefeller - Board of Trustees - Development Program - Printed Matter (Box 198, Folder 2)
    - Colleges - Princeton University - Laurance S. Rockefeller - Board of Trustees - Finances (Box 198, Folder 3)
    - Colleges - Princeton University - Laurance S. Rockefeller - Board of Trustees - Minutes-Meetings (Box 198, Folder 4, Box 199, Folder 1-3, Box 200, Folder 1-2, Box 201)
    - Colleges - Princeton University - Laurance S. Rockefeller - Contributions (Box 201, Folder 3, Box 202, Folder 1)
    - Colleges - Princeton University - Laurance S. Rockefeller - Contributions - Annual Giving - Class of 1932 (Box 202, Folder 2-3)
    - Colleges - Princeton University - Laurance S. Rockefeller - Contributions - Firestone Library Plaza (Box 202, Folder 4-5)
    - Colleges - Princeton University - Laurance S. Rockefeller - Contributions - Firestone Library - Dedication (Box 203, Folder 1-2)
    - Colleges - Princeton University - Laurance S. Rockefeller - Contributions - Princeton Education Center at Blairstown (Box 203, Folder 3)
    - Colleges - Princeton University - Laurance S. Rockefeller - Department of Philosophy (Box 203, Folder 4)
    - Colleges - Princeton University - Rockefeller Public Service Awards (Box 204, Folder 1)
    - Colleges - Princeton University - Steven Rockefeller (Box 259, Folder 1)
      Conditions Governing Access
      Restricted - Living Rockefeller family members.
    - Colleges - Radcliff College (Box 204, Folder 2)
    - Colleges - Spelman College (Box 204, Folder 3-4)
    - Colleges - Spelman College - Contributions (Box 205, Folder 1)
    - Colleges - Spelman College - Fund Raising (Box 205, Folder 2)
    - Colleges - Spelman College - Fund Raising - A-Z (Box 205, Folder 3)
    - Colleges - Spelman College - Printed Matter (Box 206, Folder 1)
    - Colleges - Stanford University (Box 206, Folder 2)
    - Colleges - State University of New York (Box 206, Folder 3)
    - Colleges - State University of New York - Nelson A. Rockefeller College of Public Affairs and Policy and Nelson A. Rockefeller institute of Government (Box 207, Folder 1)
    - Colleges - State University of New York - College at Purchase (Box 207, Folder 2)
    - Colleges - United Nations University, Tokyo (Box 207, Folder 3)
    - Colleges - United Negro College Fund (Box 207, Folder 4)
    - Colleges - University of California (Box 207, Folder 5)
    - Colleges - University of Chicago (Box 208, Folder 1)
    - Colleges - University of Chicago - Minutes-Meetings (Box 208, Folder 2)
    - Colleges - University of Pennsylvania (Box 208, Folder 3)
    - Colleges - University of Southern California (Box 208, Folder 4)
    - Colleges - University of Vermont (Box 208, Folder 5)
    - Colleges - Union Theological Seminary (Box 209, Folder 1-2)
    - Colleges - University of London - London School of Economics (Box 209, Folder 3-4, Box 210, Folder 1)
    - Colleges - University of Maryland (Box 210, Folder 2)
    - Colleges - Vanderbilt University, Nashville, TN (Box 210, Folder 3)
    - Colleges - Vassar College (Box 210, Folder 4)
    - Colleges - Wellesley College, Boston, MA (Box 210, Folder 5)
    - Colleges - Vermont Law School (Box 211, Folder 1)
    - Colleges - West Virginia Wesleyan College (Box 211, Folder 2-3)
    - Colleges - Yale University (Box 211, Folder 4-5)
    - Colleges - Yale University - Institution for Social and Policy Studies (Box 211, Folder 6)
    - Foreign Students Service (Box 212, Folder 1)
    - Foundations - A-E (Box 212, Folder 2-4)
    - Foundations - F-J (Box 213, Folder 1-4)
    - Foundations - K-N (Box 214, Folder 1-4)
    - Foundations - N-Z (Box 215, Folder 1-3)
    - Foundations - Geraldine Rockefeller Dodge Foundation (Box 215, Folder 4, Box 216, Folder 1)
    - Foundations - Ford Foundation (Box 216, Folder 2)
    - Foundations - Fund for Free Expression (Box 216, Folder 3)
    - Foundations - Funding Exchange, Inc. (Box 216, Folder 4)
    - Foundations - German Marshall Fund of the U.S. (Box 217, Folder 1-3)
    - Foundations - High Winds Funds (Box 217, Folder 4)
    - Foundations - L.A.W. Fund (Box 217, Folder 5)
    - Foundations - The Charles A Lindbergh Fund Inc. (Box 218, Folder 1)
    - Foundations - George C. Marshall Research Foundation (Box 218, Folder 2)
    - Foundations - George C. Marshall Research Foundation - Printed Matter (Box 218, Folder 3)
    - Foundations - Oceanic Institute (Box 219, Folder 1-2)
    - Foundations - Alfred P. Sloan Foundation (Box 219, Folder 3)
    - Foundations - Alfred P. Sloan Foundation - Board of Trustees (Box 219, Folder 4)
    - Foundations - Alfred P. Sloan Foundation - Finances (Investment Committee Meetings) (Box 220, Folder 1)
    - Foundations - Alfred P. Sloan Foundation - Minutes-Meetings (Box 220, Folder 2-3)
    - Foundations - Alfred P. Sloan Foundation - Printed Material (Box 221, Folder 1, Box 220, Folder 4)
    - Historical Societies - A-H (Box 221, Folder 2-4)
    - Historical Societies - I-S (Box 222, Folder 1-4)
    - Historical Societies - T-Z (Box 223, Folder 1)
    - Historical Societies - Rhode Island Historical Society (Box 223, Folder 2-4)
    - Historical Societies - Woodstock Historical Society (Box 224, Folder 1)
    - Historical Societies - Woodstock Historical Society - Frederick Billings (ship model) (Box 224, Folder 2)
    - Housing - International House - Miscellaneous (Box 224, Folder 3)
    - Housing - International House - New York (Box 224, Folder 4)
    - Housing - International House - New York - Contributions (Box 224, Folder 5)
    - Radio-Television - A-M (Box 225, Folder 1-3)
    - Radio-Television - N-Z (Box 226, Folder 1-3)
    - Radio-Television - Action for Children's Television (Box 226, Folder 4, Box 227, Folder 1)
    - Radio-Television - Educational Broadcasting Corporation - General (Box 227, Folder 2)
    - Radio-Television - Educational Broadcasting Corporation - A-Z (Box 227, Folder 3)
    - Radio-Television - Educational Broadcasting Corporation - Board of Trustees (Box 227, Folder 4)
    - Radio-Television - Educational Broadcasting Corporation - Contributions (Box 228, Folder 1-3)
    - Radio-Television - Educational Broadcasting Corporation - Fund Raising - A-Z (Box 228, Folder 4)
    - Radio-Television - Educational Broadcasting Corporation - Finances (Box 229, Folder 1)
    - Radio-Television - Educational Broadcasting Corporation - Minutes-Meetings (Box 229, Folder 2)
    - Radio-Television - Educational Broadcasting Corporation - Printed Material (Box 229, Folder 3)
    - Radio-Television - Twin Cities Public Television (Box 229, Folder 4)
    - Radio-Television - International Institute of Communications (Box 230, Folder 1)
    - Radio-Television - WGBH (Box 230, Folder 2)
    - Schools - A (Box 230, Folder 3)
    - Schools - B-C (Box 231, Folder 1-3)
    - Schools - D-L (Box 232, Folder 1-4)
    - Schools - M-N (Box 233, Folder 1-3)
    - Schools - N-P (Box 234, Folder 1-4)
    - Schools - Q-Z (Box 235, Folder 1-4)
    - Schools - Brearley School (Box 236, Folder 1)
    - Schools - The Buckley School in the City of New York (Box 236, Folder 2)
    - Schools - Choate Rosemary Hall (Box 236, Folder 3-4)
    - Schools - Deerfield Academy (Box 236, Folder 5)
    - Schools - Good Hope School (Box 237, Folder 1-3)
    - Schools - Hawaii Preparatory Academy (Box 238, Folder 1-2)
    - Schools - Hurricane Island Outward Bound School (Box 238, Folder 3)
    - Schools - Loomis Institute (Box 238, Folder 4)
    - Schools - Madeira School (Box 238, Folder 5)
    - Schools - Mannes College of Music (Box 239, Folder 1)
    - Schools - Midwest Academy (Box 239, Folder 2)
    - Schools - Navajo Community High School (Box 239, Folder 3)
    - Schools - North Country School (Box 239, Folder 4)
    - Schools - Phillips Academy (Box 239, Folder 5)
    - Schools - Phillips Exeter Academy (Box 240, Folder 1)
    - Schools - Pocantico Hills Central School District (Box 240, Folder 2)
    - Schools - Reading is Fundamental (Box 240, Folder 3, Box 241, Folder 1)
    - Schools - Skowhegan School of Painting and Sculpture (Box 241, Folder 2-3)
    - Schools - United World Colleges Inc. (Box 241, Folder 4-5)
    - Schools - Washington County Vocational Technical School (Box 241, Folder 6)
    - Schools - Woodstock Country School (Box 242, Folder 1-3)
  - Energy, 1977-1981; 14
    - Energy - A-G (Box 243, Folder 1-5)
    - Energy - H-P (Box 244, Folder 1-5)
    - Energy - P-Z (Box 245, Folder 1-3)
    - Alliance to Save Energy (Box 245, Folder 4-5, Box 246, Folder 1)
    - Alliance to Save Energy - Printed Matter (Box 246, Folder 2)
    - Center for Renewable Resources (Box 246, Folder 3)
    - Citizens' Energy Project, Inc. (Box 246, Folder 4)
    - Designwrights' Collaborative (Box 247, Folder 1)
    - Energy Conservation Coalition, Inc. (Box 247, Folder 2)
    - Energy Systems Research Group, Inc. (Box 247, Folder 3)
    - Fund for Secure Energy (Box 248, Folder 1-2)
    - Fund for Secure Energy - Contributions, 1979-1981 (Box 248, Folder 3)
    - Golden Gate Energy Center (Box 248, Folder 4)
    - Health and Energy Learning Project (Box 249, Folder 1)
    - National Public Power Institute (Box 249, Folder 2)
    - Northeast Appropriate Technology Network (Box 249, Folder 3)
    - Northeastern Legislative Energy Staff (Box 249, Folder 4)
    - Nuclear Information and Resource Service (Box 249, Folder 5, Box 250, Folder 1)
    - Pacific Alliance (Box 250, Folder 2)
    - Printed Material (Box 250, Folder 3)
    - Safe Energy Communications Council (SECC) (Box 250, Folder 4)
    - United States Government - Executive Office of the President - Energy Policy Planning (Box 250, Folder 5)
    - Willrich, Mason (Box 250, Folder 6)
    - World Information Service on Energy (WISE) (Box 251, Folder 1)
  - F-I, 1977-1981; 15
    - F - Miscellaneous (Box 251, Folder 2-3)
    - G - Miscellaneous (Box 251, Folder 4)
    - Geriatrics (Box 252, Folder 1-2)
    - H - Miscellaneous - Ha (Box 252, Folder 3)
    - H - Miscellaneous - Hb-Hz (Box 253, Folder 1-2)
    - Horticulture - A-H (Box 253, Folder 3-4)
    - Horticulture - I-Z (Box 254, Folder 1)
    - Horticulture - Pacific Botanical Garden (Box 254, Folder 2)
    - Horticulture - The New York Botanical Garden (Box 254, Folder 3)
    - I - Miscellaneous (Box 254, Folder 4)
    - International Basic Economy Corporation (IBEC) (Box 255, Folder 1)
    - International Basic Economy Corporation (IBEC) - Anderson (Box 255, Folder 2)
    - International Basic Economy Corporation (IBEC) - Merger - Booker McConnel Limited (Box 255, Folder 3, Box 256, Folder 1-2)
    - International Basic Economy Corporation (IBEC) - Finances (Box 256, Folder 3-4)
    - International Basic Economy Corporation (IBEC) - Finances (Box 259, Folder 2)
    - International Basic Economy Corporation (IBEC) - Minutes-Meetings (Box 257, Folder 1-3, Box 258, Folder 1-2)
    - International Basic Economy Corporation (IBEC) - Monthly Reports (Box 258, Folder 3)
  - International Relations, 1977-1981; 16
    - International Relations - A-I (Box 260, Folder 1-4)
    - International Relations - I-S (Box 261, Folder 1-4)
    - International Relations - T-Z (Box 262, Folder 1)
    - American Universities Field Staff (Box 262, Folder 2)
    - Amnesty International (of U.S.A.) (Box 262, Folder 3)
    - (The) English Speaking Union (Box 262, Folder 4)
    - Atlantic Council of the United States (Box 263, Folder 1)
    - Federal Union, Inc. (Box 263, Folder 2)
    - International Rescue Committee, Inc. (Box 263, Folder 3)
    - Radio Free Europe, Inc. (Box 264, Folder 1-2)
    - Spanish Institute (Box 264, Folder 3)
    - World Affairs Council of Philadelphia (Box 264, Folder 4)
    - Africa - African American Institute (Box 264, Folder 5)
    - Africa (Box 265, Folder 1)
    - Africa - Liberia (Box 265, Folder 2)
    - Africa - South Africa (Box 265, Folder 3)
    - Americanism (Box 265, Folder 4)
    - Asia - A-Z (Box 266, Folder 1)
    - Asia - Agricultural Development Council, Inc. (Box 266, Folder 2)
    - Asia - Agricultural Development Council, Inc. - Finances (Box 266, Folder 3)
    - Asia - Agricultural Development Council, Inc. - Contributions (Box 266, Folder 4)
    - Asia - Agricultural Development Council, Inc. - Minutes-Meetings (Box 267, Folder 1)
    - Asia - Agricultural Development Council, Inc. - Printed Material (Box 267, Folder 2)
    - Asia - Asia Society - A-Z (Box 267, Folder 3)
    - Asia - Asia Society - New Building (Box 267, Folder 4-5)
    - Asia - Asia Society - Contributions, 1972-1982 (Box 268, Folder 1-2)
    - Asia - Asia Society - Contributions - Asian Art Collection (Box 268, Folder 3)
    - Asia - Asia Society - Minutes-Meetings (Box 268, Folder 4)
    - Asia - Asia Society - Printed Material (Box 268, Folder 5)
    - Asia - Asia Society - Fund Raising (Box 268, Folder 6)
    - Asia - Asia Society - Dinners-Receptions (Box 269, Folder 1)
    - Asia - Asia Society - Williamsburg VII - Australia, 1977 November 1-4 (Box 269, Folder 2)
    - Asia - Asia Society - Williamsburg VIII (Box 269, Folder 3)
    - Asia - Asia Society - Williamsburg IX (Box 269, Folder 4)
    - Asia - Asian Cultural Council (Box 269, Folder 5)
    - Asia - Citizens Commission on Indochinese Refugees (Box 270, Folder 1)
    - Canada (Box 270, Folder 2)
    - China (Box 270, Folder 3)
    - Cuba (Box 270, Folder 4)
    - Egypt (Box 270, Folder 5)
    - Europe - A-Z (Box 270, Folder 6)
    - Foreign Aid (Box 270, Folder 7)
    - Foreign Aid - Care-Medico (Box 270, Folder 8)
    - Foreign Aid - Meal for Millions-Freedom from Hunger Foundation (Box 271, Folder 1)
    - Foreign Aid - Overseas Development Council (Box 271, Folder 2)
    - Foreign Aid - Oxfam America, Inc. (Box 271, Folder 3)
    - Foreign Policy (Box 271, Folder 4)
    - Foreign Policy - Council on Foreign Relations (Box 272, Folder 1-3)
    - Foreign Policy - Council on Foreign Relations - Board of Directors (Box 272, Folder 4)
    - Foreign Policy - Council on Foreign Relations - Contributions (Box 272, Folder 5)
    - Foreign Policy - Council on Foreign Relations - Finances (Box 272, Folder 6)
    - Foreign Policy - Council on Foreign Relations - Meetings (Box 273, Folder 1)
    - Foreign Policy - Council on Foreign Relations - Printed Matter (Box 273, Folder 2)
    - Foreign Policy - Council on Foreign Relations - Fundraising, 1979-1980 (Box 273, Folder 3)
    - Foreign Policy - Council on Foreign Relations - Special Project (Box 274, Folder 1)
    - Foreign Policy - Council on Foreign Relations - Annual Giving Campaign, 1980 (Box 274, Folder 2)
    - Foreign Policy - Council on Foreign Relations - Nominating Committee-Membership (Box 274, Folder 3)
    - Foreign Policy - Council on Foreign Relations - 1980's Project (Box 274, Folder 4)
    - Foreign Policy - Council on Foreign Relations - Acquisition of houses from CIAR (Box 274, Folder 5)
    - Foreign Policy - Council on Foreign Relations - Building-Purchase Fund (Box 275, Folder 1)
    - Foreign Policy - Council on Foreign Relations - Annual Giving Campaign (Box 275, Folder 2-4, Box 276, Folder 1)
    - Foreign Policy - Council on Foreign Relations - Nominating Committee-Membership (Box 276, Folder 2)
    - Foreign Policy - Council on Foreign Relations - Foreign Affairs Article - The Shah in Perspective (Box 276, Folder 3)
    - Foreign Policy - Foreign Policy Association (Box 276, Folder 4)
    - France - A-Z (Box 276, Folder 5)
    - France - French-American Foundation (Box 277, Folder 1)
    - Germany (Box 277, Folder 2)
    - India (Box 277, Folder 3)
    - Israel (Box 277, Folder 4)
    - Italy (Box 277, Folder 5)
    - Japan - A-Z (Box 277, Folder 6)
    - Japan - Japan Center for International Exchange (Box 278, Folder 1)
    - Japan - Japan Society - A-Z (Box 278, Folder 2)
    - Japan - Japan Society - Board of Directors (Box 278, Folder 3)
    - Japan - Japan Society - Dinners-Luncheons (Box 278, Folder 4)
    - Japan - Japan Society - Annual Dinners (Box 278, Folder 5)
    - Japan - Japan Society - Contributions (Box 279, Folder 1-2)
    - Japan - Japan Society - Finances-Budget (Box 279, Folder 3)
    - Japan - Japan Society - Fund Raising (Box 279, Folder 4)
    - Japan - Japan Society - Intellectual Interchange Program (Box 279, Folder 5)
    - Japan - Japan Society - Japan Foundation (Box 279, Folder 6)
    - Japan - Japan Society - Minutes-Meetings (Box 280, Folder 1)
    - Japan - Japan Society - Printed Matter (Box 280, Folder 2-3)
    - Korea (Box 280, Folder 4)
    - Pan American - Center for Inter American Relations Inc. (CIAR) (Box 280, Folder 5, Box 281, Folder 1)
    - Pan American - Center for Inter American Relations Inc. (CIAR) - Board - Richard E. Salomon, 1977-1980 (Box 281, Folder 2-5, Box 282, Folder 1)
    - Pan American - Center for Inter American Relations Inc. (CIAR) - Pete Collado Retirement Luncheon, 1981 July 21 (Box 282, Folder 2)
    - Pan American - Center for Inter American Relations Inc. (CIAR) - Contributions (Box 282, Folder 3)
    - Pan American - Center for Inter American Relations Inc. (CIAR) - 52 and 54 East 68th Street (Box 282, Folder 4)
    - Pan American - Center for Inter American Relations Inc. (CIAR) - Finances - Richard E. Salomon, 1977-1981 (Box 283, Folder 1-3)
    - Pan American - Center for Inter American Relations Inc. (CIAR) - Fund Raising - Richard E. Salomon, 1977-1978, 1980-1981 (Box 283, Folder 4, Box 284, Folder 1-4, Box 285, Folder 1)
    - Pan American - Center for Inter American Relations Inc. (CIAR) - General, 1979-1981 (Box 285, Folder 2-4)
    - Pan American - Center for Inter American Relations Inc. (CIAR) - Printed Matter (Box 286, Folder 1)
    - Pan American - Center for Inter American Relations Inc. (CIAR) - Real Estate - Richard E. Salomon (Box 286, Folder 2)
    - Pan American - Council of the Americas, 1981 (Box 286, Folder 3)
    - Pan American - The Americas Society (Box 286, Folder 4)
    - Pan American - The Americas Society - Board of Directors - Minutes-Meetings (Box 287, Folder 1)
    - Pan American - The Americas Society - Fund Raising (Box 287, Folder 2)
    - Pan American - The Americas Society - Canadian program - David Rockefeller presides, 1981 September 30 (Box 287, Folder 3)
    - Pan American - Potential Merger of CIAR with Council of Americas (Box 287, Folder 4)
    - Pan American - The Americas Society (Box 287, Folder 5)
    - Pan American - A-Z (Box 288, Folder 1-2)
    - Pan American - Brazil (Box 288, Folder 3)
    - Pan American - Chile (Box 288, Folder 4)
    - Pan American - Pan American Society of the U.S. (Box 288, Folder 5)
    - Pan American - Panama Canal Treaties (Box 289, Folder 1)
    - Peace - A-N (Box 289, Folder 2-4)
    - Peace - P-Z (Box 290, Folder 1-3)
    - Peace - American Committee on East-West Accord (Box 290, Folder 4)
    - Peace - Bilderberg Conference (Box 290, Folder 5, Box 291, Folder 1-2)
    - Peace - Council for a Livable World Education (Box 291, Folder 3)
    - Peace - Fund for Peace (Box 291, Folder 4)
    - Peace - Institute for World Order (Box 291, Folder 5)
    - Peace - Institute for Defense and Disarmament Studies (Box 292, Folder 1)
    - Peace - International Physicians for the Prevention of Nuclear War, Inc. (Box 292, Folder 2)
    - Peace - National Mobilization for Survival (Box 292, Folder 3)
    - Peace - National Peace Academy Campaign (Box 292, Folder 4)
    - Peace - Northern Ireland (Box 292, Folder 5)
    - Peace - Sane (Box 293, Folder 1)
    - Thailand (Box 293, Folder 2)
    - Union of Soviet Socialist Republics (USSR) (Box 293, Folder 3)
    - United Nations - A-Z (Box 293, Folder 4-5)
    - United Nations - Executive Council on Foreign Diplomats (Box 294, Folder 1)
      Scope and Contents
      Formerly Travel Program for Foreign Diplomats
    - United Nations - Executive Council on Foreign Diplomats - Printed Material (Box 294, Folder 2)
    - United Nations - Printed Material (Box 294, Folder 3)
    - United Nations - United Nations Association of the USA (Box 294, Folder 4)
    - United Nations - United Nations Association of the USA - Printed Material (Box 295, Folder 1)
    - United Nations - UNICEF (Box 295, Folder 2)
    - United State Government - Department of State - General (Box 295, Folder 3)
    - United States Government - Department of State - Fine Arts Committee (Box 295, Folder 4)
    - United States Government - Agency for International Development (AID) - International Executive Service Corps (IESC) (Box 296, Folder 1)
    - United States Government - AID - International Executive Service Corps (IESC) - Finances (Box 296, Folder 2)
    - United States Government - AID - International Executive Service Corps (IESC) - Minutes-Meetings (Box 296, Folder 3-4)
    - United States Government - AID - International Executive Service Corps (IESC) - Printed Material (Box 297, Folder 1)
    - United States Government - AID - International Executive Service Corps (IESC) - Special Review Committee (Box 297, Folder 2)
    - United States Government - AID - International Executive Service Corps (IESC), 1980-1982 (Box 297, Folder 3-4)
  - J-M, 1977-1981; 17
    - J - Miscellaneous (Box 298, Folder 1)
    - K - Miscellaneous (Box 298, Folder 2)
    - L - Miscellaneous (Box 298, Folder 3-4)